<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<search>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>我的2023年</title>
    <link href="/2023/07/15/%E4%B8%AA%E4%BA%BA%E6%97%A5%E5%BF%972023/"/>
    <url>/2023/07/15/%E4%B8%AA%E4%BA%BA%E6%97%A5%E5%BF%972023/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>2023.7.16.<br>Whoa, at this point I suppose I can try to type something, cause I am now at this piont going on a brand new tour another time and it really feels like kind weird, exciting stimulating or addictive. I am on the train, or the highspeed train to Nanking, and this time I will meet with a cute and well educated and well mannered, maybe kind sophisticated little girl, but not quite little, if compared to my age could be describe as an junior. But I suppose I am young as well, just very a few years elder than her. And because of this, I have to take a little bit of more consideration.</p><p>And I will go meet with my Bangladesh friend this time as well, and I will also bring him to greet with my internet female friend. Maybe I can introduce them to have some simple and interesting conversation. </p><p>And now, I am on the highspeed train, this time I bought the first class, the first class is not quite expansive as I imagned before, only a few 20 percent more than the normal one. But it actually feels not bad, the air conditioning here is quite effective and strong,</p><p>And when I am walking around, walking outside, especially when I am inside a group of people, I am always likely to possess some very delicate and unexplicable feeling, and which is kind of very strong feeling as well, which would almost strangle your soul or breath, a very formidable yoke that likely to make you be overwelmed. To describe it simply and as accurately as I can, it is mainly the feeling of trenmendous gap or even an abyss  between myself and this world, especially the world of people, but not the world of universe. On the contrary, I can always strongly feel my connection with the space and time. During these days , I am trying to learn, to grasp and understand the meaning of relativity from the most beginning. Now, I can grasp and understand some of the most basic and shattered pieces, which at least is true as well. The most overwhelming thing that I learned is about the time, the illusion, and the hulluciantion of time. I remembered that Eninstein said, “Time is the most stubborn illusion, it dosen’t really exist , it is hallucinatory.” And I kind doubt what is the feel right at that moment when Eninstein discovered this as trueth, but my own feeling is that, this is just horrifying , at least to the one that represents myself at the point of time, it is just horrifying, I am really afraid of the unreal thing, we are not really, all the things are just hallucination, how frightening this just is.</p><p>Nothing, nothing, just could possibly be explained.</p><p>Damn it, now an obese  girl just sat by myside, I discriminate them, these days  find that that I’m not that quite nervous with the girls, cause I know that they do not have the mysterity that I use to imagine, they are just simply organized, without much complex, but from a higher stratosphere, I think all the people are almost just the same to me, maybe there would be slighly different in their complexion or oufit, but insdie a deeper insight they are just in are kind of universal uniform, totally the same, no matter their gener, age, genre, ethnic, the language they speak, the color of their skin, their height all weight, their voice etc. But I would really be interested to meet with people like Albert Enenstein or Sergei Rachmaninoff. Some of though the very few of the brains are destined to be speccially designed at the beginning. And now my heart is slightly aching. During these years, or to say around 2 or three years ago, I found that sometimes my heart would ache, and this is a horryffing sign that symblyse the beggining of my aging, I am becoming old now, and someday I will day and decay into minor pieces.</p><p>I hate it, but I dont suppose there’s the need. You don’t just have to hate and love as well. There isn’t really exsit the true meaning or final purpose for the love or hatred. Nothing really matters. They would disappear so fast and entirely, as never once existed or happened once before. Thus, the grievement or the gaiety is the kind of temporary illusion as well.</p><p>2023.7.17.</p><p>今天和一位对文学非常有天赋和想法的尊贵优雅的贵族少女进行了一次高端的文化座谈交流，前天晚上她说她在南京，然后向我提议能否与我真实的相见，所以前天晚上我就够买了昨天晚上的高铁票来到了南京，今天是17号，中午我们品味了美味的海鲜自助，非常感谢这位女孩的款待，现在我们进行了一些很有趣的文化和知识层面的交流。</p><p>2023.7.20.</p><p>极其地感谢吴可以提供给我这个编辑性，自由度非常高的可以通过文字和图片来表达的平台，虽然也许我想更多时候我使用文字也许就足够了，我要让自己慢慢学习着习惯和使用这个平台，用它来更好的整理自己的思绪。</p><p>已经快要有整整三年了， 我仍然在如此无可救药的（这是无可救药吗？）地思念着芥，有时候我看入我镜子中的模样，更多的时候我只是会感到困惑，我想我并不是美丽的，但是姐姐也同样不是，如果使用惯常的那种标准，我们两个都并不是美丽的。我想很多时候我想我是有那种自信说，我的文字是描述性，文学性非常强的，可是当我想要描写和姐姐有关的一些东西，我的情感变得太过纯粹和强烈的以致于我几乎无法正常地写出我惯常使用的优雅文字了。</p><p>有些时候我做了一些似乎罪恶的事情，不过也许那并不是我自己的罪恶，我只是一个被动承担第三方罪恶的载体，所以也是无辜的。</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>Odyssey</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>cafe girl skating</title>
    <link href="/2023/07/15/cafe%20girl%20skating/"/>
    <url>/2023/07/15/cafe%20girl%20skating/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>昨天晚上带她去万象城，(The Mix C)吃了一些东西，然后带她滑冰，她说这是她第一次滑冰，我也是。我发现滑冰和我原来想的不太一样，或者说没有我原来想象的那样有趣，虽然也并不是太无聊，但是没有那样极其的有趣，然后是，感觉非常的累，也可能是我还完全不熟悉。另外我发现滑冰鞋的冰刀和我原来想的也不太一样，没有我原来想象的那么锋利，底部是一条有一定宽度（虽然也非常的窄）的片状金属。</p><p>我比她熟悉的快一点，所以我滑的快一些，她滑的更慢，有点像在蹒跚学步，有几个瞬间我想搀扶一下她，但是又感觉非常的犹豫，不过最终她没有摔倒，但是有几次似乎看起来险些要摔倒了。</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>Cafe girl</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>by cafe girl</title>
    <link href="/2023/07/12/cafegirl/"/>
    <url>/2023/07/12/cafegirl/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>第二天和他学英语，怎么说，这是一件很奇妙的缘分或者说是事情，暑期的咖啡店兼职期间，开始了每天学习英语的日子，还挺有意思的，感觉自己很久没有这样如此规律的学习过了，难得哈哈。</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>Cafe girl</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Jayscat123</title>
    <link href="/2023/07/11/123/"/>
    <url>/2023/07/11/123/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>今天吴陈添帮我配置了我的个人网站</p><p>我爱他</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>Coursework</category>
      
      <category>Computer Network</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>我的2022年</title>
    <link href="/2023/07/11/%E4%B8%AA%E4%BA%BA%E6%97%A5%E5%BF%972022/"/>
    <url>/2023/07/11/%E4%B8%AA%E4%BA%BA%E6%97%A5%E5%BF%972022/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>待整理</p><p>今年一整年都在疯狂思念那个我完全无法见到甚至想象到的虚幻个体，是虚幻的吗？</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>Odyssey</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>cafe girl 教学日志</title>
    <link href="/2023/07/11/cafe%20girl%202/"/>
    <url>/2023/07/11/cafe%20girl%202/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>2023年7月11日</p><p>教学计划，学生的词汇量较为薄弱，所以我决定先提升学生的词汇量，学生目前的词汇量在1500左右，我认为至少需要帮她提升2000个词汇。但是两千是一个比较大的数量，所以我想分批来做，先试着讲500到1000个词汇。</p><p>此外我不太想使用非常原始的一个一个背的方法，但是如果是独自学习也许会这样记忆，但是因为学生有一个教学能力非常强的辅导，我想挑选一些合适的文章和她一起阅读。我给学生买了笔记本，一本空白，一本线格，一本小本子，也就是从前我背词用的那种，她可以随身携带，用于巩固一些词汇。</p><p>2023年7月13日</p><p>今天已经让学生比较系统的认识了解了整个四级考试试卷的题型和结构。</p><p>她现在对作文，听力，阅读，翻译四个大的题型的考察方式，板块时间，有了比较明确的认识。</p><p>今天教会了学生使用tiktok，然后介绍指导她在tiktok上学习英语，通过比较有趣的方式。</p><p>今天带学生初步比较具体地了解了一个听力的题型，学生的能力比我原先设想的好很多。</p><p>接下来需要大量加强学生的词汇，今天和继续介绍了更多的词汇，并且逐渐加强，加大加强学习量。</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>Cafe girl</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>1.1</title>
    <link href="/2023/07/11/1/1.1/"/>
    <url>/2023/07/11/1/1.1/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="1"><a href="#1" class="headerlink" title="1."></a>1.</h1><h2 id="1-1"><a href="#1-1" class="headerlink" title="1.1."></a>1.1.</h2>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  
</search>
