<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<search>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>我的2023年</title>
    <link href="/2023/07/15/%E4%B8%AA%E4%BA%BA%E6%97%A5%E5%BF%972023/"/>
    <url>/2023/07/15/%E4%B8%AA%E4%BA%BA%E6%97%A5%E5%BF%972023/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>2023.7.16.<br>Whoa, at this point I suppose I can try to type something, cause I am now at this piont going on a brand new tour another time and it really feels like kind weird, exciting stimulating or addictive. I am on the train, or the highspeed train to Nanking, and this time I will meet with a cute and well educated and well mannered, maybe kind sophisticated little girl, but not quite little, if compared to my age could be describe as an junior. But I suppose I am young as well, just very a few years elder than her. And because of this, I have to take a little bit of more consideration.</p><p>And I will go meet with my Bangladesh friend this time as well, and I will also bring him to greet with my internet female friend. Maybe I can introduce them to have some simple and interesting conversation. </p><p>And now, I am on the highspeed train, this time I bought the first class, the first class is not quite expansive as I imagned before, only a few 20 percent more than the normal one. But it actually feels not bad, the air conditioning here is quite effective and strong,</p><p>And when I am walking around, walking outside, especially when I am inside a group of people, I am always likely to possess some very delicate and unexplicable feeling, and which is kind of very strong feeling as well, which would almost strangle your soul or breath, a very formidable yoke that likely to make you be overwelmed. To describe it simply and as accurately as I can, it is mainly the feeling of trenmendous gap or even an abyss  between myself and this world, especially the world of people, but not the world of universe. On the contrary, I can always strongly feel my connection with the space and time. During these days , I am trying to learn, to grasp and understand the meaning of relativity from the most beginning. Now, I can grasp and understand some of the most basic and shattered pieces, which at least is true as well. The most overwhelming thing that I learned is about the time, the illusion, and the hulluciantion of time. I remembered that Eninstein said, “Time is the most stubborn illusion, it dosen’t really exist , it is hallucinatory.” And I kind doubt what is the feel right at that moment when Eninstein discovered this as trueth, but my own feeling is that, this is just horrifying , at least to the one that represents myself at the point of time, it is just horrifying, I am really afraid of the unreal thing, we are not really, all the things are just hallucination, how frightening this just is.</p><p>Nothing, nothing, just could possibly be explained.</p><p>Damn it, now an obese  girl just sat by myside, I discriminate them, these days  find that that I’m not that quite nervous with the girls, cause I know that they do not have the mysterity that I use to imagine, they are just simply organized, without much complex, but from a higher stratosphere, I think all the people are almost just the same to me, maybe there would be slighly different in their complexion or oufit, but insdie a deeper insight they are just in are kind of universal uniform, totally the same, no matter their gener, age, genre, ethnic, the language they speak, the color of their skin, their height all weight, their voice etc. But I would really be interested to meet with people like Albert Enenstein or Sergei Rachmaninoff. Some of though the very few of the brains are destined to be speccially designed at the beginning. And now my heart is slightly aching. During these years, or to say around 2 or three years ago, I found that sometimes my heart would ache, and this is a horryffing sign that symblyse the beggining of my aging, I am becoming old now, and someday I will day and decay into minor pieces.</p><p>I hate it, but I dont suppose there’s the need. You don’t just have to hate and love as well. There isn’t really exsit the true meaning or final purpose for the love or hatred. Nothing really matters. They would disappear so fast and entirely, as never once existed or happened once before. Thus, the grievement or the gaiety is the kind of temporary illusion as well.</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>Odyssey</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>by cafe girl</title>
    <link href="/2023/07/12/cafegirl/"/>
    <url>/2023/07/12/cafegirl/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>第二天和他学英语，怎么说，这是一件很奇妙的缘分或者说是事情，暑期的咖啡店兼职期间，开始了每天学习英语的日子，还挺有意思的，感觉自己很久没有这样如此规律的学习过了，难得哈哈。</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>Cafe girl</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>Jayscat123</title>
    <link href="/2023/07/11/123/"/>
    <url>/2023/07/11/123/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>今天吴陈添帮我配置了我的个人网站</p><p>我爱他</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>Coursework</category>
      
      <category>Computer Network</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>cafe girl 教学日志</title>
    <link href="/2023/07/11/cafe%20girl%202/"/>
    <url>/2023/07/11/cafe%20girl%202/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>2023年7月11日</p><p>教学计划，学生的词汇量较为薄弱，所以我决定先提升学生的词汇量，学生目前的词汇量在1500左右，我认为至少需要帮她提升2000个词汇。但是两千是一个比较大的数量，所以我想分批来做，先试着讲500到1000个词汇。</p><p>此外我不太想使用非常原始的一个一个背的方法，但是如果是独自学习也许会这样记忆，但是因为学生有一个教学能力非常强的辅导，我想挑选一些合适的文章和她一起阅读。我给学生买了笔记本，一本空白，一本线格，一本小本子，也就是从前我背词用的那种，她可以随身携带，用于巩固一些词汇。</p><p>2023年7月13日</p><p>今天已经让学生比较系统的认识了解了整个四级考试试卷的题型和结构。</p><p>她现在对作文，听力，阅读，翻译四个大的题型的考察方式，板块时间，有了比较明确的认识。</p><p>今天教会了学生使用tiktok，然后介绍指导她在tiktok上学习英语，通过比较有趣的方式。</p><p>今天带学生初步比较具体地了解了一个听力的题型，学生的能力比我原先设想的好很多。</p><p>接下来需要大量加强学生的词汇，今天和继续介绍了更多的词汇，并且逐渐加强，加大加强学习量。</p>]]></content>
    
    
    <categories>
      
      <category>Cafe girl</category>
      
    </categories>
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  <entry>
    <title>1.1</title>
    <link href="/2023/07/11/1/1.1/"/>
    <url>/2023/07/11/1/1.1/</url>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1 id="1"><a href="#1" class="headerlink" title="1."></a>1.</h1><h2 id="1-1"><a href="#1-1" class="headerlink" title="1.1."></a>1.1.</h2>]]></content>
    
    
    
  </entry>
  
  
  
  
</search>
